Finding Aid for the Sterling Silliphant Papers, 1957-1985
UCLA Library, Department of Special Collections
- Motion Picture Screenplays
  - Shaft in Africa
    - undated., Screenplay, typescript, holograph corrections. (Box 40)
    - Correspondence (Box 40)
    - News clippings. (Box 40)
    - 1972 September 12, Two copies of carbon of screenplay (Box 58)
    - 1972 September 12, Typescript with holograph corrections of screenplay. (Box 58)
    - 1972 September 12, Three copies of typescript screenplay (Box 58)
    - 1972 November 1, Carbon [screenplay] (Box 59)
    - 1972 November 18, Typescript [screenplay] (Box 59)
    - 1972 November 1, Three copies of typescript [screenplay] (Box 59)
    - 1972 September 15, Three copies of typescript screenplay (Box 59)
    - 1972 September 15, Typescript with holograph corrections of screenplay. (Box 59)
    - 1972 November 20, Typescript with holograph corrections [screenplay] (Box 60)
    - undated., Typescript with holograph corrections [screenplay] (Box 60)
    - 1972 November 18, Typescript [screenplay] (Box 60)
  - Shaft in Asia
    - (Box 40)
      Newsclippings.
  - Shaft's Big Score
    - Correspondence (Box 40)
    - Newsclippings. (Box 40)
  - Shaft's Triple Cross
    - 1971 December 14, Typescript [screenplay] (Box 58)
    - 1971 December 22, Typescript [screenplay] (Box 58)
    - Three folders of miscellaneous sections, typescript carbon with holograph corrections. (Box 58)
  - Silent Flute, Addition, 11/82.
    - Memorandum of agreement, writing agreement, correspondence, assignment of rights. v.p., ca. 1969-1973.; 13 items. (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Joint venture agreement, production correspondence. v.p., 1971-1978.; ca. 30 items. (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Narrative script. n.p., 1970 October 19; by Stirling Silliphant.; i-ii. pp, 1-70. Transcript (multilith) (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Narrative script. n.p., 1970 October 19; by Stirling Silliphant.; i-v. pp, 1-70. Transcript (multilith) (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Outline of characters. n.p., 1970 October 19; 5 leaves. Typescript (photocopy). Incomplete. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1973 August 3; by Stirling Silliphant.; 77 pages. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1973 September 20; by Stirling Silliphant.; 69 pages. Typescript. (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1973 September 20; by Stirling Silliphant.; 69 pages. Typescript (photocopy). (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1973 September 21; by Stirling Silliphant.; Typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1973 September 21; by Stirling Silliphant.; Typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. Another copy. (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Squaw Fever
    - Screenplay. 2 copies. (Box 34)
  - The Big Bamboo
    - undated., Typescript [screenplay]. (Box 38)
    - (Box 38)
      General correspondence; Workups of story under various titles.
  - The Inheritors (When I Was Young...), Versions of the screenplay produced as The Inheritors, each screenplay or section incorporating changes of the previous versions.
    - When I Was Your Age... Harold Robbins's "The Inheritors.", 1970 January 28; Screenplay by Stirling Silliphant.; [4 folders] Typescript multilith. Four copies. (Box 74, Folder 1-4)
    - Harold Robbins's "The Inheritors.", 1970 January-April; Screenplay by Stirling Silliphant.; [2 folders] (Box 75, Folder 1-2)
      - Harold Robbins's "The Inheritors", 1970 January 28; Screenplay by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript multilith with holograph notation on title page. (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Harold Robbins's "The Inheritors", First revised: 1970 April 20; Screenplay by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Revised pages of screenplay organized by stage of revision., 1970 January 23-April 17; In four folders. (Box 75, Folder 3-7)
      - Revised pages, "first draft.", 1970 January 16; [pencilled revision to January 23, 1970] Typescript with hologrpah corrections. (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Revised pages., 1970 January 23; Typescript (carbon). (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Revised pages., 1970 April 13; Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Revised pages, "first revised.", 1970 April 17; Typescript (carbon). (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Revised pages., undated. (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Production notes., ca. 1970; 5 items. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - The Joe Louis Story
    - Correspondence, etc. relating to motion pictures, 1 folder. (Box 25)
    - Clippings of reviews and publicity material., In a black scrapbook. (Box 123)
  - The Liberation of Lord Byron Jones, Harvest-Pingree Productions.
    - 1968 December 4., 2 copies of the "fourth draft" of the screenplay. (Box 23-24)
      (Based on the novel by Jesse Hill Ford).
    - undated, 2 copies of the screenplay. (Box 23-24)
    - 1969 March 15., 2 copies of the screenplay, one incomplete. (Box 23-24)
    - 1969 January 6., 1 copy of the screenplay. (Box 23-24)
    - 1968 October 31., 2 copies of the screenplay. (Box 23-24)
    - 1969, Scripts. (Box 31)
    - Correspondence., 2 folders. (Box 37)
    - Financial statements (Box 37)
    - Estimated cost sheets (Box 37)
    - Publicity. (Box 37)
    - (Box 38)
    - undated., Two copies. (Box 41)
    - Typescript with holograph corrections [screenplay]. (Box 41)
  - The Little Sister, Katzka-Berne Productions, Inc.
    - 1968 May 15., 4 copies of screenplay, one incomplete. (Box 22-23)
      (Based on the novel by Raymond Chandler).
    - 1968 May 15., 1 screenplay with holograph corrections. (Box 22-23)
    - 1968 May 6., 1 screenplay. (Box 22-23)
    - 1967 June 30., 1 screenplay (photocopy). (Box 22-23)
    - 1967 October 3., 1 screenplay. (Box 22-23)
    - 1 folder of various pages, corrections and insertions. (Box 22-23)
    - 1967 June 30., 3 copies of the screenplay (carbon), one with holograph corrections. (Box 22-23)
    - Correspondence, etc. relating to motion pictures, 1 folder. (Box 25)
    - 1967 June 28., Typescript screenplay. (Box 41)
  - The Shape of Nightmares
    - undated., Typescript section with holograph corrections. (Box 43)
    - 1971 August 18, Revised typescript section. (Box 43)
    - 1971 August 13, Revised typescript section. (Box 43)
    - 1971 August 12., Revised typescript section. (Box 43)
    - 1971 August 9, Revised final draft, typescript [screenplay] (Box 43)
    - Revised typescript carbon. (Box 43)
    - 1971 August 2., Revised typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 43)
  - The Slender Thread, Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, Inc.
    - 1965 March 22, 1 screenplay. (Box 18-19)
      (title: Call Me Back!)
    - undated, 1 typescript screenplay with holograph corrections. (Box 18-19)
      (under final title: The Slender Thread)
    - 1964 November 6, 2 screen treatments. (Box 18-19)
      (under former title: A Voice On the Wind)
    - 1965 May 10, 1 screenplay (incomplete copy). (Box 18-19)
    - 1965 March 15, 1 typescript screenplay with holograph corrections. (Box 18-19)
    - 1964 December 15, 1 scene breakdown. (Box 18-19)
    - 1964 November 6., 1 typescript of screen treatment with holograph corrections. (Box 18-19)
    - 1964 November 6., 1 typescript of screenplay with holograph corrections. (Box 18-19)
      (under former title: The Willow Plate)
    - 1965 March 15, 3 copies of first draft screenplay. (Box 18-19)
      (under former title: Cross My Heart and Hope To Die)
    - 1 folder. (Box 18-19)
      Contains correspondence, contracts, film changes, etc.
    - 1964 November 6., 1 typescript (carbon) of screenplay. (Box 18-19)
    - Correspondence, etc. relating to motion pictures, 1 folder. (Box 26)
      Miscellaneous.
    - Correspondence, etc. relating to motion pictures, 1 folder. (Box 26)
      Call sheets.
    - Correspondence, etc. relating to motion pictures, 1 folder. (Box 26)
      Productions estimates.
    - Correspondence, etc. relating to motion pictures, 1 folder. (Box 26)
      Status reports.
    - Correspondence, etc. relating to motion pictures, 1 folder. (Box 26)
      "A.D. reports."
    - Correspondence, etc. relating to motion pictures, 1 folder. (Box 26)
      Scene breakdowns.
    - Correspondence, etc. relating to motion pictures, 1 folder. (Box 26)
      Material dealing with Seattle.
  - The Swarm, Addition, 11/82.
    - Treatment. n.p., undated.; by Stirling Silliphant; 14 pages. Typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Treatment. n.p., undated.; by Stirling Silliphant; 19 pages. Typescript (photocopy) with this: Another copy. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Treatment. n.p., undated.; by Stirling Silliphant; 108 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Treatment. n.p., undated.; by Stirling Silliphant; 109 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections.. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Step-outline. n.p., 1974 July 3; 398 pages. Typescript with holograph corrections.. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Treatment. n.p., 1974 July 3; by Stirling Silliphant; 40 pages. Typescript. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Treatment. n.p., 1974 July 3; by Stirling Silliphant; 40 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Revised treatment. n.p., 1974 August 16; by Stirling Silliphant; 120 pages. Typescript with holograph corrections.. (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Revised treatment. n.p., 1974 August 16; by Stirling Silliphant; 118 pages. Typescript. (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Revised treatment. n.p., 1974 August 16; by Stirling Silliphant; 118 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Treatment. n.p., 1974 August 27; by Stirling Silliphant; 108 pages. Typescript. (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Treatment. n.p., 1974 August 27; by Stirling Silliphant; 108 pages. Typescript (photocopy). [2 copies] (Box 82, Folder 3-4)
    - Treatment. n.p., 1976 September 10; by Stirling Silliphant; 102 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Treatment. n.p., 1976 September 10; by Stirling Silliphant; 102 pages. Typescript (photocopy). (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Treatment. n.p., 1976 September 10; by Stirling Silliphant; 108 pages. Typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Treatment. n.p., 1976 September 17; by Stirling Silliphant; 102 pages. Typescript. (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Treatment. n.p., 1976 September 17; by Stirling Silliphant; ca 40 pages. Typescript (photocopy), holograph, with holograph corrections. (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Treatment. n.p., 1976 September 17; by Stirling Silliphant; pages 1-7, 1-102. Typescript (multilith). with printed cover. [2 copies] (Box 82, Folder 10-11)
    - Treatment. n.p., 1976 September 17; by Stirling Silliphant; 19 leaves, variously numbered. Typescript (carbon). (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Treatment. n.p., 1976 September 17; by Stirling Silliphant; ca. 40 leaves, variously numbered. Typescript (carbon). (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Mixed sets. n.p., 1974 September; by Stirling Silliphant; ca. 140 pages. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Mixed sets. n.p., 1974 September; by Stirling Silliphant; ca. 140 pages. Typescript (carbon). (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 September; by Stirling Silliphant; 65 pages. Typescript. First draft. (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay. n.p., undated.; by Stirling Silliphant; 65 pages. Typescript (photocopy) (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 September; by Stirling Silliphant; 138 pages. Typescript with holograph corrections. First draft. (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 September; by Stirling Silliphant; 139 pages. Typescript (carbon) First draft. (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 September; by Stirling Silliphant; 202 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. First draft. (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 October 8; by Stirling Silliphant; 184 pages. Typescript. First draft. (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 October 8; by Stirling Silliphant; 184 pages. Typescript (carbon). First draft. (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 November 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 36 pages. Typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. First revised screenplay. (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 November 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 35 pages. Typescript. First revised screenplay. (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 November 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 34 pages. Typescript (carbon). First revised screenplay. (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 November 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 26 pages. Typescript (photocopy). First revised screenplay. (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 November 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 150 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. First revised screenplay. (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 November 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 149 pages. Typescript. First revised screenplay. (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1974 November 29; by Stirling Silliphant; 149 pages. Typescript (carbon). First revised screenplay. (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1975 January 15; by Stirling Silliphant; 159 pages. Typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. Second revised screenplay. (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1975 January 15; by Stirling Silliphant; 144 pages. Typescript. (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1975 January 15; by Stirling Silliphant; 144 pages. Typescript (carbon). Second revised screenplay. (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1975 January 15; by Stirling Silliphant; 144 pages. Typescript (multilith). Second revised screenplay. (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Outline of sequences and characters. n.p., 1976 July 27; by Stirling Silliphant; 40 pages. Typescript, typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Outline of sequences and characters. n.p., 1976 July 27; by Stirling Silliphant; 30 pages. Typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections on cover. (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Outline of sequences and characters. n.p., 1976 August 27; by Stirling Silliphant; 31 pages. Typescript (photocopy). (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1976 December 22; by Stirling Silliphant; 149 pages. Typescript (photocopy), typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. First draft screenplay. (Box 85, Folder 6)
      Includes revised pages, 12/17/82-12/19/76.
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1976 December 22; by Stirling Silliphant; 146 pages. Typescript. First draft screenplay. (Box 85, Folder 7)
      Includes revised pages, 10/18/76-1/5/77.
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1976 December 22; by Stirling Silliphant; 149 pages. Typescript (photocopy), typescript (multilith). First draft screenplay. (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1976 December 22; by Stirling Silliphant; 146 pages. Typescript (photocopy), typescript (multilith). First draft screenplay. (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1976 December 22; by Stirling Silliphant; 146 pages. Typescript (carbon). First draft screenplay. (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1977 January; by Stirling Silliphant; 156 pages. Typescript (multilith). (Box 86, Folder 2)
      With printed cover: Warner Bros./presents/Irwin Allen's production of /The Swarm/ written by Stirling Silliphant.
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1977 March 30; by Stirling Silliphant; 159 pages. Typescript, typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. Revised screenplay. (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1977 March 30; by Stirling Silliphant; 157 pages. Typescript (carbon). Revised screenplay. (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1977 March 30; by Stirling Silliphant; 157pages. Typescript (multilith). Revised screenplay. (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1977 March 30; by Stirling Silliphant; ca. 50 pages. Typescript with holograph notes. Revised screenplay. (Box 86, Folder 6)
      Revisions, 4/6/77, 4/7/77.
    - The Swarm. n.p., 1977 April; Written by Stirling Silliphant; 157pages. Typescript (multilith). With cover. Second draft. (Box 86, Folder 7-8)
      Revisions, 5/10/77-5/26/77.
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1977 April; by Stirling Silliphant; ca. 50 pages. Typescript (carbon). Shooting final screenplay. (Box 86, Folder 9)
      With note attached: "Pinks--put into other carbons."
    - Screenplay. n.p., 1977 April; by Stirling Silliphant; 157 pages. Typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. Shooting final screenplay. (Box 87, Folder 1)
      Revisions, 4/6/77-4/7/77.
    - The Swarm. n.p., 1977 August.; Written by Stirling Silliphant; 138 pages. Typescript (multilith). Shooting final. With cover. (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - The Swarm. n.p., 1977 August.; Written by Stirling Silliphant; [140 pages.] Typescript (multilith). Revised shooting final. With cover. [2 copies.] (Box 87, Folder 3-4)
    - Characters. n.p., undated.; 6 leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Characters. n.p., undated.; 6 leaves. Typescript. (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Characters. n.p., undated.; ca. 100 leaves. Typescript, typescript (carbon), typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections. (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Characters. n.p., ca. 1976 July; 6 pages. Typescript (carbon) (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - With this: Memo to Irwin Allen. n.p., 1976 July 1; 1 leaf. Typescript (carbon). (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Cast and bits list. n.p., 1977 August 16; 2 pages. Typescript (multilith). (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Staff and crew list. n.p., 1977 August 16; 2 pages. Typescript (multilith). (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Shooting schedule. n.p., 1977 August 15; 63 pages. Typescript (multilith). (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Revised pages. n.p., 1974 December 6; ca. 100 leaves. Typescript. (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - With this: Carbons of revised pages., ca. 100 leaves. (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Revised pages. n.p., 1974 December 6; ca. 75 leaves. Typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - With this: additional copies of revised pages., ca. 75 leaves. (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Revised pages. n.p., 1976 August, October; ca. 60 pages. Typescript, typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Revised pages. n.p., 1977 May; 140 pages. Typescript, typescipt (carbon), typescript (photocopy) with holograph corrections.. (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Revised pages. n.p., 1977 May-September; ca. 130 pages. Typescript, typescipt (carbon), typescript (photocopy), typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Revised pages. n.p., undated.; ca. 150 pages. Typescript, typescipt (carbon), typescript (photocopy), typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous pages. n.p., undated.; ca. 200 pages. Typescript, typescipt (carbon), typescript (multilith) with holograph corrections. (Box 88, Folder 7)
      Incomplete treatment and screenplay.
    - Miscellaneous pages. n.p., undated.; ca. 200 pages. Typescript (carbon), typescript (multilith). (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - The Towering Inferno, Versions of the screenplay eventually produced as "The Towering Inferno." Screenplays and sections are arranged in chronological order of revision; each screenplay incorporates changes of the previous versions.
    - The Tower., Stern, Richard.; 374 p. Typescript photocopy. Novel. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - The Glass Inferno., Scortia, Thomas and Frank M. Robinson.; 540 p. Typescipt multilith. Novel. In three folders. (Box 63, Folder 2-4)
    - The Glass Inferno., Scortia, Thomas and Frank M. Robinson.; Typescipt multilith. Outline of novel organized by scene and character. With orange cover. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Call sheets. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Meeting and production notes. (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Synopsis of scenes. (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Synopsis, 3" x "5 notecards. Typescript. (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Synopsis, Photocopy on notecards on letter-sized paper. (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Synopsis, Photocopy on notecards on letter-sized paper with holograph corrections. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Revised pages of screenplay., 8 folders. (Box 64, Folder 4-8, Box 65, Folder 1-4)
      Revised pages of screenplay organized by date and stage of revision, from 19 July 1973 through 24 July 1974.
      - Revisions., 1973. (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Revisions., 1974 January. (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Revisions., 1974 February. (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Revisions., 1974 March. (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Revisions, 1974 April. (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Revisions, 1974 May. (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Revisions, 1974 June. (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Revisions, 1974 July. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Revised pages of screenplay. Miscellaneous pages., In 4 folders. (Box 65, Folder 5-8)
      - Miscellaneous pages for opening scenes. (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous pages for scenes with dialog: scenes numbered. (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous pages for scenes with dialog: scenes numbered. (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous pages for scenes with dialog: scenes unnumbered. (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - "The Glass Tower.", 1973 July 12.; Irwin Allen's production; Typescript photocopy with holograph corrections. With plastic cover. (Box 66, Folder 1)
      Cast of characters, story line and items for development.
    - The Glass Inferno, 1973 July-August; [6 folders] (Box 66, Folder 2-6)
      - Step-outline, 1973 August 15; by Stirling Silliphant; [pencilled revision to 8-17-73] Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Step-outline, 1973 August 17; by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript. (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Step-outline, 1973 August 17; by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript photocopy. Title page missing. (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Step-outline, 1973 August 17; by Stirling Silliphant; [pencilled notation: Revised 8-20-73] Typescript carbon. (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Step-outline, 1973 August 17; by Stirling Silliphant; [pencilled revision to "The Towering Inferno"] [pencilled notation: Revised 8-2073] Typescript and typescript photocopy with holograph corrections. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - The Towering Inferno, 1973 August 23; [5 folders] (Box 66, Folder 7-11)
      - Step-outline, by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Step-outline, by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript carbon. (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Step-outline, by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript multilith. With green cover. (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Step-outline, by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript multilith with holograph corrections. With green cover. (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Step-outline, by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript multilith with holograph corrections. With green cover. (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - The Towering Inferno, 1973 September 7; [3 folders] (Box 67, Folder 1-3)
      - Screen treatment, by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Screen treatment, by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript. (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Screen treatment, by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript carbon. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - The Towering Inferno, 1973 October-1974 January; [27 folders] (Box 67, Folder 4-6, Box 68, Folder 1-5, Box 69, Folder 1-8, Box 70, Folder 1-7, Box 71, Folder 1-2)
      - Screenplay, 1973 October 19; by Stirling Silliphant; [pencilled revision to 10-26-73.] Typescript with holograph corrections. Notation "Pink (1)." (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Screenplay, 1973 October 26; by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript. Notation "Pink (1)." (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Screenplay, 1973 October 26; by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript carbon. Notation "Pink (1)." (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Screenplay, 1973 October 26; by Stirling Silliphant; Typescript photocopy (Box 68, Folder 1)